"Previously on The Mentalist..."
Yeah. Lena's on a short list
for a position
in the Commerce Department in D.C.
It's not a done deal yet.
I have to be confirmed,
and that could take months.
This is Bill Peterson,
San Antonio DEA.
What does this guy Peterson
have on you?
When I was your boss at Rio Bravo
I had your back.
You telling me
you don't have mine now?
Jane, I'm on the 6th floor now.
Lisbon, it looks like he may be
at the other end. Keep going.
You took me off on purpose.
You have to let me do my job.
If you can't, how do we work together?
Peterson can end my career.
I can go to prison.
Any mention of this could end things
for Lena before it even starts.
Well, you can't let him do it.
It's over for you. And your wife.
I'm gonna see to that.
"Everything turned out
exactly as we planned."
- I know.
- No one was hurt.
- Well, except the bad guy, of course
but he was an assassin.
I understand. Mission accomplished.
But in the middle of our mission
you directed me to go somewhere
that had nothing to do
with the mission.
Yeah, I was concerned
about your safety.
- You don't get it.
- I don't get what?
- I'm an FBI agent.
- Uh, I think I do get that.
- No, I don't think you do.
- Excuse me.
Wiley?
You asked me to keep tabs on Peterson
let you know if he's making
any suspicious moves.
- "Yeah. What's he done?"
- According to his credit card record
two days ago he bought a plane ticket
to Mexico. He flew there this morning.
Well, he might have gone
down there for work.
I checked. His office said
he's at a conference in St. Paul.
Okay, well, could you look
into Peterson's phone records for us?
We'll be right in.
- What am I looking for?
- Well, something fishy.
"Fishy. Got it."
Is that about Abbott?
- Sounds like it.
- Well, what are we gonna do?
Whatever we can.
Peterson's checked into a hotel
just outside Rio Bravo.
That's where he worked
with Abbott, right?
- Yeah, ten years ago.
- I checked his phone record.
The only call that stuck out
was to a San Antonio Congressman
this afternoon--
representative Jules Blatt.
I've heard of him.
He's a nobody trying to make
a name for himself.
Well, if he could block
Lena Abbott's confirmation
it would buff his reputation
in certain circles, wouldn't it?
How would Peterson going
to Rio Bravo help that?
I don't know.
The hearings start in four days
so if Peterson wants to make trouble
now is the time to do it.
Well, what are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do
about what?
Why is everyone whispering?
How do you know about all this?
Wylie's keeping tabs on Peterson.
And you brought Wylie into it?
Well, I mentioned that Peterson
might be making some trouble.
He volunteered. The kid
wouldn't take no for an answer.
Do you have any idea
what Peterson is doing in Rio Bravo?
Peterson's careful.
He wouldn't make any accusations
if he didn't have the evidence
to back it up.
I shot a man.
Bullet's in the body.
Peterson found the corpse,
dug out the bullet
all he's gotta do is subpoena the gun
and... that's game over.
I need to call Lena.
I'll let you do that.
What does he think Peterson
has on him?
- The bullet.
- Well, if he does, then Abbott's toast.
That's a little pessimistic.
But this isn't just
about Lena's confirmation.
Abbott will lose his job.
He could go to prison.
I don't think that's gonna happen.
- Why not?
- We'll prevent it.
In four days? How?
I'm not quite sure yet.
Jane, this is serious.
I know. Don't you love it
when the stakes are high?
I came as soon as I could.
Thanks for coming, honey.
Let's talk in my office.
Peterson?
Yes.
- You're sure he has the evidence?
- Sure enough.
Look, baby, I am so sorry.
I should've told you everything
from the start.
- Don't say that.
- No, no, no, it's my fault.
- I really let you down.
- Do not say that.
You don't have to apologize, not to me.
Not to anyone.
That this person
would try to bring you down
makes me so angry.
- This is simple. I'll withdraw my name.
- No.
I don't want the job
if this is what it takes to get it.
Look, I'm not gonna have you quit
because of me. Okay?
Now, I-I'll tell Peterson I'll resign.
- Absolutely not.
- We can just go along with the same story
- that we're separated, and maybe--
- Excuse me?
Jane, could you please
just give us a minute, please?
Yeah, I would, but time is short
and I'm guessing that each of you
is offering to fall on your sword
for the other, which is very
loving and admirable
- but I don't think it'll work.
- Why not?
Because Peterson is ruthless
and determined
and he won't stop
until he's destroyed both of you.
Now we knew he was gonna make
a move like this sooner or later.
- Now it is time for us to make our move.
- Which is what, exactly?
The hearings are in three days.
Well, I think I can come up
with something if...
you both want me involved.
No, no, this is--
this is not your problem.
Wait a minute. Dennis tells me
you have one of the trickiest
and most devious minds he's worked with.
He did, did he? Ah.
Well, I didn't come here to be
flattered, but, please, go on.
He also says you're his friend
and that he would trust you
with his life.
- Can you really help?
- I think so.
Dennis.
What do you have in mind?
I can't tell you.
We need your hands to be clean.
Deniability and such.
Okay, we'll do it your way.
Excellent.
Hey, any updates?
Peterson arrived back
in San Antonio two hours ago.
Has he had any more contact
with Congressman Blatt?
No, it's just the one
phone call yesterday.
It lasted 30 seconds. It was probably
just a voice mail message.
I hear Abbott's in trouble.
I'm not very good
at keeping secrets.
Good thing you're in the FBI
- What are we doing about it?
- Jane's coming up with a plan right now.
You might wanna think twice
before getting in on this one.
Both of you.
I have a feeling we're gonna be
pretty far outside the lines.
Well, Jane had me pretend
to kill a guy once.
Are we going further outside
the lines than that?
Probably not.
Then I'm good.
Me, too.
Let's take this outta the bullpen.
What did Abbott say?
- All systems go.
- Great.
- So what do you got, Wylie?
- Bill Peterson is 55 years old.
He's been a DEA agent for 27 years.
Married briefly in his 30s.
His ex-wife lives in Tacoma.
No kids, no living relatives.
- What does he like doing?
- Work, mostly.
Plays a little tennis,
goes scuba-diving in the Caribbean.
Based on what he buys at the local
liquor store, he's a wine snob.
- Interesting.
- Why?
Obviously he's as corrupt
as the day is long.
- Why obviously?
- Well, a man that likes tennis
travel, and a good Bordeaux
isn't retiring on a government pension.
He has some loot stashed someplace.
We need to find it.
What about the evidence
Peterson found in Mexico?
The bullet--
what are we gonna do about that?
I'll take care of the bullet.
You dig down on Peterson.
He's been a DEA agent for 30 years.
There's a ton of ways
he could be stealing.
He could be taking payoffs from a cartel
he could be selling the drugs himself.
Yeah, look into stuff like that.
I have to go make some calls
and catch up with an old friend.
- Hi.
- We catch a case?
- No.
- What are you all working on?
Nothing.
Sure looks like something.
Anything I can do to help?
Yeah.
You can hold down the fort out here.
- Did I do something wrong?
- No. Just stay out here, okay?
Mr. Barsocky.
You crazy circus freak.
Patrick Jane, you son of a bitch.
Looking good, Pete. Very relaxed.
Well, I'm as a fat and wrinkled
as Daisy the amazing elephant, but thanks.
And thanks for paving the way to Austin.
First class tickets and everything.
You should see that hotel room
you paid for.
Well, that is my pleasure, Pete.
How's things?
You know. Looking for rubes to fleece.
You?
I'm-I'm seeing someone
at the moment, actually.
You dog.
Wait, is it that pretty brunette
that came around with you
a couple years ago--
the cop?
- As a matter of fact, it is.
- I knew it.
I could tell she was sweet on you.
Well, she's a little cranky
with me right now.
Women. Who gets 'em?
But I'm happy to hear it.
You should have someone, Patrick.
You deserve to be happy.
Thank you.
Maybe it's time, you know?
Take the ring off.
No shame in moving on.
Angela would want you to.
Yeah. Thanks, Pete.
I need a favor.
I have a friend who's in a little trouble
with the law
and I want to get him out of it.
- Sounds like fun to me.
- That's what I thought.
So, here's the gag...
That's all fine, but I need
those other files.
Yeah, get me the--
the second quarter arrest figures
on my desk in the morning, all right?
- Yeah. See you then.
- Sir? Excuse me?
This is a private club. You can't--
Sir?
- Sir?
- Who let you in?
Oh, I'm just taking a little look around
thinking about membership.
Is that supposed to be amusing?
Mr. Peterson, this man said
that he was from your office.
Is there a problem?
It's fine, Stacey.
Stacey, Mr. Peterson and I go
way back. Thank you.
How was your little trip down
to Rio Bravo?
- You know about that?
- Of course I do.
You think I'm gonna sit back
and watch you destroy Dennis Abbott?
I'm not trying to destroy anyone.
I'm after justice.
Dennis Abbott murdered
a man in cold blood.
A commander of one of the largest
drug cartels in Mexico.
Murdered him nonetheless.
Don't you have better things
to do, Peterson?
Like update your tennis gear?
What is this?
Oh, it's velour.
Let me tell you something, Jane.
I don't give a rat's ass
about Dennis Abbott.
- I see an opportunity.
- How do you figure?
There's a new wave coming into D.C.
If I can help a Congressman
do something opportune, uh--
block an appointment
that his party is desperate to kill, say--
he's in my debt.
It's money in the bank.
The future, Jane.
That's what I'm thinking about.
Screwing Dennis Abbott--
that's just icing on the cake.
It won't work.
- We'll see.
- Yes, we will.
We shall see.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Peterson.
He was very persuasive.
Stacey...
Have you seen my cell phone?
Um... No.
Morning.
Here.
Thanks.
Did you get anything off the phone?
I pulled all of Peterson's contacts
and cross-referenced them
with our database.
I checked his call history,
his e-mails, his texts...
- And?
- Nothing.
Nothing that looks like contact
with a cartel member.
If Peterson's getting money
under the table
I don't know who's giving it to him.
Cho and I couldn't find anything, either.
We looked into offshore corporations
third parties' accounts.
There's no sign that money's
being hidden or laundered.
Well, of course not. He knows
that's the first place someone would look.
So where is he putting the money?
Got me. Nothing about him
really sticks out
except that he's super diligent.
Works 60 hours a week or more
and two to three times a month
he goes out with the teams on raids.
What kinda raids?
E-mails mention low-level busts--
neighborhood labs, local dealers.
Low-level busts?
That doesn't sound like Peterson.
Yeah, he wouldn't get his hands dirty
unless there was something in it for him.
- I'll bet he's skimming.
- By George, I think she's got it.
- Skimming what?
- When a raid goes down
the DEA agent arrests the dealers
"and then they process
the cash and the drugs"
"that have been seized."
"The senior agent is supposed to record
the amount of money and drugs"
'from the crime scene
before it's put into evidence."
"Unless he's taking some for himself."
"Nobody knows."
If the drug dealer complains,
nobody believes him.
It's kinda the perfect crime.
10,000 here, 50,000 there.
He could have millions by now.
Yeah, but where is he hiding
the money?
Based on the security app
on Peterson's phone
it looks like his house has
a crazy elaborate security system.
Well, there's your answer.
The money's in the house.
If we could get our hands
on that cash
and prove that Peterson's stealing
we'd put an end to this right now.
I don't see how we get in the house.
It's like Fort Knox,
and we only have 48 hours.
Don't be defeatist. Can you pull up
the plan of the security system?
Yeah, I think so.
- Bill Peterson.
- "Hello, Mr. Peterson."
"This is Missy Brammer. I'm Congressman
Blatt's legislative director."
I'm following up
on your call of a few days back.
Uh, as I mentioned, I'd very much like
to speak to Congressman Blatt
about the nomination
of Lena Abbott to the commerce post.
"Yes, the Congressman
was intrigued by your message."
"He'd like to know more."
He's in D.C. right now,
as the hearings are in two days.
"Could you and I meet this evening
to discuss it?"
- Yeah, well, that'd be fine.
- "Good."
8:00 p.m. at the Wagon Wheel
on Alamo.
- "I'll make a reservation."
- See you then.
The good news is Peterson's house
is only one floor
and is easily accessed from the street.
Well, what's the bad news?
There are 17 security cameras
six motion sensors, and one cat.
I hate cats. They always try to jump
on me.
Oh, what about the security system?
I downloaded an app from his phone
that monitors the cameras.
I can hack into the forensic software
and get at the root folders.
If he checks in remotely,
it'll look like no one's in the house
but I'll need to do it from here.
- Can you turn off the alarm?
- You'll need to do that at the house.
I can't do it with the phone.
- Hi.
- I'd like to speak to Cho, please.
Sure.
Cho.
What's up?
Something's obviously going on
and I'm here to protest my exclusion.
- Vega.
- Jane is planning something
and I'm pretty sure it has to do
with whatever's going on with Abbott.
- Don't worry about it.
- I do, though.
If Abbott's in trouble, I wanna help.
No.
- You're letting Wylie help.
- Wylie's different.
- I don't feel responsible for him.
- You're not responsible for me.
Vega, if this goes wrong,
it's a career killer.
You'll be finished at the FBI
before you even get started.
I'll take that risk.
What we're discussing involves
breaking about seven laws.
As long as it's only seven.
Either I'm a part of this team,
or I'm not.
We need eyes on Bill Peterson.
Where he's going, what he's doing.
- You think you can do that?
- Absolutely.
- Go.
- Thank you, sir.
Don't call me "sir".
- Vega.
- Sir.
Where are you going?
Just running an errand.
Jane, my office, please.
- Where's Lena?
- I just dropped her off at the airport.
She's headed back to D.C.
What's going on?
Well, like I said, I--
I can't really let you in on it.
Okay, I assume you're breaking
every rule and regulation the FBI has.
Well, that's a little over the top.
Look, I know I said we'd do it
your way
but I-I've changed my mind.
I can't have my people taking risks
like this on my behalf.
I'll take what comes.
And your wife?
- I think I can keep her out of it.
- You know that's not true.
What you did at Rio Bravo--
you risked your life
to take out a mass murderer
that no one else could...
No one else would.
You did that 'cause you're a good man.
Peterson is not a good man.
He's a greedy, corrupt bureaucrat
with a very healthy sprinkling
of sociopath on top.
- I can handle Peterson.
- No, you won't.
And if we stop now, you're going to prison
your wife's gonna lose her career
and Peterson is on his way
to being the head of the DEA.
Is that what you want?
It's not what I want.
And for what it's worth
everyone else feels the same way.
It's gonna be fine.
Chin up.
Trust.
"Obviously, the hearings are this week"
and Dennis Abbott is very much
in our sight.
The issue of what happened
at Rio Bravo
will be key to stopping
Lena Abbott's confirmation.
I'm so glad we're on the same page.
Well, a hearing's a tricky thing.
Really it's about showmanship.
You display it--
a little theatrics, if you will.
It is D.C. after all.
As it happens, Ms. Brammer
I have something you can use.
Would you be able to bring it
to the office tomorrow?
I would.
Good.
Cho, it's happening tomorrow.
Whatever you're planning,
we have to do it now.
I'm connected
to Peterson's security system.
Looks like he's getting ready to leave.
Wylie, it's your time.
Just give me a minute.
Okay, we're good to go.
If Peterson checks his cameras,
he'll see a static image
showing no activity
in or outside the house.
Great.
But I can only hold it
for about an hour and a half.
Well, that should give us
enough time.
So what's your plan?
Well... Pick the lock
open the door, see what happens.
- What'll happen is the alarm will go off.
- Not right away.
Alarms give you a minute
to 90-second grace period
before they alert anyone.
That should give me enough time
to figure out the passcode.
Figure it out how?
The way I figure things out.
That's your plan?
Yeah, pretty much.
60 seconds.
Yeah, nothing like a little adrenaline
to get the mind fired up.
I'm gonna need some quiet.
- Cat alert, nine o'clock.
- Yeah, I'm not touching that.
Time's running out.
Have a little faith.
- There. Got it.
- How'd you do that?
- Well--
- Wylie texted it to him.
- No, he didn't.
- When he hacked into the security system
he saw Peterson punch in the code.
I saw you looking at your phone.
Lisbon, you're killing the magic here.
- Can we get moving?
- Sure.
Remember, he's not gonna hide
the money
in or under his mattress.
- Hidden compartments, false drawers.
- All over it.
We got guns, no money.
If the money's here someplace,
we can't find it.
Jane?
Candlesticks seem a little odd,
don't they?
I don't understand.
I mean, for a thin strip
of Texas leather like Peterson.
Doesn't strike me
as the candlestick type.
Maybe he hired a designer.
Maybe.
China.
- Oh, this is a problem.
- Don't you know how to open a safe?
Biometrics. We need
Peterson's thumbprint to open that.
Well, what are we gonna do?
- Okay, so we go to the backup plan.
- What's that?
We have about 40 minutes left.
If we can't get to Peterson's money,
we'll use our own money.
What money?
Uh, Wylie, I need you to get
into the evidence room
and get us some cash.
How much?
At least a million dollars.
Two would be better.
That's... big. I'm--
I'm not sure how I'd do that.
Do your best.
Yeah, it's very important.
I don't have clearance for that.
Let me, uh...
Let me think.
I'll get back to you.
Sir.
What is it?
You know how Jane said
he wouldn't need your help?
He lied, didn't he?
- What's up, Wylie?
- Vega, is Peterson still at Blatt's office?
"Yeah. He just got there."
Any chance he'll go to work
when he's done?
I called his office. They said
he's not expected in today. Why?
I'm going to San Antonio.
"It's gonna take me
about 40 minutes to get there."
If Peterson leaves in the next
half an hour, stall him, okay?
Stall him? Uh, okay.
Stall him.
Oh, my God, I am so sorry!
I'll get you my insurance!
Did you see that?
Could've been worse.
You stop short?
No, I didn't stop short!
She ran right into me!
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?
How do I know?
You ran right into me!
You'll wanna fill out a report
for your insurance.
Oh, for God's sake!
- Is there a problem?
- I--
I know I just got them renewed.
I put them in here.
I took out the old ones.
- Put the new ones in.
- Miss?
I just feel so terrible about this.
I know you!
You're one of Abbott's people.
Agent Peterson?
Oh, now I am really embarrassed.
I am so sorry, sir. Uh--
The sun was in my eyes and I thought
you were a lot further away from me.
Look, uh, just--
just forget about it.
Oh, no, sir, we--
we could never do that.
There is so much damage
- to your car here.
- I'm not worried about it.
We really should fill out
a report, though.
- Your car really looks terrible.
- I'm in a hurry!
"I tried to stop him,
but he wouldn't stay."
- Which way's he heading?
- East. He's headed your way.
"Well, how far are you?"
About 15 minutes. How far is Wylie?
About 15 minutes.
I got here as fast as I could.
Thank you.
Good luck. Bye.
Obviously the issue with protected
zones is colored by money
- but we're gonna have to--
- Mrs. Abbott.
Dennis?
Linda, I'll catch up with you later.
Oh... Baby.
- What are you doing in D.C.?
- Well, I wanted to see you.
And I know you're scared.
- More like terrified.
- Well, don't be.
I trust Jane.
And he hasn't let me down so far.
Dennis, we need a miracle.
Listen. You will be confirmed.
And we'll be together.
I have to go.
The hearing's about to start.
Okay, I'll walk you in.
I have something to do inside anyway.
Abbott.
- Funny meeting you here.
- Well, I could say the same thing, Bill.
I guess you haven't heard.
It's not official yet,
but I'm gonna be a witness
at your wife's hearing.
Ah. Well, who did that?
Blatt.
Representative Jules Blatt
put your name on the list
to be a witness?
I have evidence he thinks
people should hear about.
I think you know what it is.
Evidence, huh?
Evidence that you brought him?
What is this, Abbott?
What are you doing?
You know, maybe I should talk to Blatt.
You see, I have evidence, too.
Yeah. Take a look.
Now that's nice.
Okay, that's the best one right there.
What, Bill?
Wait, Bill?
Seems we both have secrets.
Cute kitty, by the way.
- Put your hands up.
- You think I'm wearing a wire?
Up!
Come on, Bill!
This is just a conversation
between two old friends, right?
You broke into my home.
I have people that will account
for every minute of my time.
If it wasn't you, then it was Jane
or one of those other idiots.
That's a crime, not to mention
illegal search.
Well, that'll be for the D.A. to sort out.
But it will get the attention
of the Inspector General.
And there will be an internal investigation
and they'll look into all of your old busts
and realize that you have been
a thief for 20 years.
I have you, Bill.
I have you by the short and curlies.
Okay.
Okay. Fine.
Take half.
We both walk away. This is over.
Wow. Half.
- How much is half?
- About 800.
So you're offering me $800,000
of the cash that you've been skimming?
- You're not getting a dime more.
- I don't want any more.
Hello again, Agent Peterson.
I have all I need.
It doesn't matter what you do to me.
- It can't help.
- Why not?
Blatt has the bullet.
The bullet you shot into that Zeta's head.
Bullet.
Was that the evidence
you were talking about?
That's right. And when Blatt
gets done with it
your wife can kiss
her new job goodbye.
And you're going to prison, my friend.
- Abbott, Peterson, Vega.
- Hey.
Uh, good to see you all.
All me to introduce Congressman Blatt's
legislative director, Missy, um...
- Uh... I'm sorry. What is it?
- Uh, Brammer.
Sorry. Missy Brammer.
Uh, you said you had a constituent
who had to see me?
Yes, Miss Brammer.
This is Bill Peterson.
He is one of the Congressman's
most enthusiastic supporters.
- Oh, how do you do?
- Yeah, wait, wait... no.
This isn't right.
- I'm sorry?
- There's been a mistake.
I met Missy Brammer
two days ago in San Antonio.
Well, that's impossible, because
Miss Brammer's been here in D.C.
all week
preparing for the hearings.
Uh, which I'm gonna be late for
if I don't hurry.
- Okay.
- Nice to meet you all.
Mr. Peterson.
Hey. Wait--
No, no, no.
She returned my call from Blatt's office.
"Hi. My cell phone just died.
Could I use one of yours?"
"Sure. Missy's outta town.
You can use hers."
- "Thank you very much."
- "You're welcome."
- "Bill Peterson."
- "Hello, Mr. Peterson."
"This is Missy Brammer."
"I'm Congressman Blatt's
legislative director."
I met her! In Blatt's office.
"Sorry, everybody. Pest control.
We need the office for 20 minutes."
"All right. Everybody out.
They gotta spray."
- "Hey. Hello."
- "Come in."
- "I got something for you."
- "Thank you."
"Here we go."
Bill?
I can't tell you how much
it means to me to say this.
You're under arrest.
Wonderful to see the government
at work.
- Guys, let me drive you to the airport.
- Nah, you've done enough already.
- Well, thank you for everything.
- Aw...
You know what?
That was some good, clean fun.
- Like old times.
- Just like old times.
Pete, hold the door a sec.
He tells me you got a sweetheart.
That little brunette?
That is true.
Don't screw it up, Patrick.
- I'll try not to.
- Life's too short.
See ya.
- Bye.
- Come on...
"Careful there. Now don't spill any."
- Um...
- Plastic cups?
Okay. A toast.
To friends.
Thank you for... all...
- We are forever in your debt.
- Yes, yes.
We are forever in your debt.
I-I make horrible speeches.
- I'm so sorry.
- Cheers. Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Let's go check out that waffle truck.
- Oh, definitely.
So how fast were you going
when you drove to San Antonio?
Like a hundred million miles an hour.
Roughly.
How fast were you going when you
rammed the back of Peterson's car?
- Like 3 miles an hour.
- Still, I bet it was pretty cool.
It was. It was really cool.
You know, I don't want a waffle.
You wanna dance?
No. No, I'm--
I'm a terrible dancer.
Oh, come on.
What do you have to lose, Wylie?
Come on. Let's go.
Okay, but you can't laugh.
No promises.
Well, since everything
is cleared up with Lena
I'll be moving in a couple of months
work from the D.C. office.
So you know what that means.
It's you.
- What is?
- The unit.
It's yours.
You'll be in charge.
I talked to the regional office
I talked to the assistant director
and everyone agrees.
You've earned it, Kimball.
And I think you're gonna do
a great job at it.
Thank you, sir.
No. Thank you.
Well, since that's settled, I think
I am going to dance
with the next undersecretary
of the department of commerce.
Get on the dance floor, baby.
Come on.
- Congratulations, Cho.
- Thank you.
You deserve it.
I'm gonna go get another taco.
Okay.
You know, we never finished
our conversation.
No, it got busy.
- Life throws you curve balls.
- Are we talking about baseball now?
I'm serious. I want us
to be strong together.
We are, aren't we?
I love you, and I also love
what I do.
You can't be jealous of that.
Oh, it's not that.
What is it?
What?
I don't wanna lose you.
I don't know how I would react.
- You're not gonna lose me.
- You don't know that.
Nobody knows what's gonna happen.
You could die tomorrow.
I could.
We need to focus on
what's going on right now.
Right here. It's good.
It is very, very good.
Yeah.
Okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Do you wanna dance?
- Here? In front of everyone?
- Sure.
- Okay, one dance.
- Two.
Everything is a negotiation
with you.
Come on.